Guide to the Yonkers Police Department Records 1867-1907 MS 296
New-York Historical Society
Yonkers Police Department records
1867-1907
New-York Historical Society
Yonkers (N.Y.). Police Department
MS 296
50.5 Linear feet (407 volumes)
This collection consists primarily of police blotters detailing arrests and other police activities of the Yonkers Police Department between 1867-1935 (with gaps). Also included are several volumes of Board of Police minutes and resolutions, and a force book listing the department officers and providing some background information.
Arrangement Note
The material has been arranged by format into two series: Series I, Yonkers Police Blotters, and Series II: Minute Books, Order Books, and Force Book. Volumes are arranged chronologically. (Volume 407 of the collection was found on the shelves and added to the collection in 2020; that number is between volumes 47 and 48).
Scope and Contents Note
This collection includes police blotters dating November 16, 1867-January 6, 1907 (incomplete); three minute books, Board of Police Commissioners, April 20, 1881-July 21, 1903; order books, April 10, 1871-August 8, 1905; and a Force Book, circa 1880's, listing officers alphabetically by shield number, name, residence, occupation, and nativity.
The 403 volumes of the police blotters provide a chronological list of police activities, including roll calls, arrest of "prisoners," and detention of "lodgers" who were apparently sheltered in the precinct. In the police blotters, there are letters regarding complaints of various crimes committed throughout Yonkers and neighboring areas such as Bronxville. These letters range from general descriptions of the crime and the person responsible. Other letters have descriptive details of the perpetrator such as their height, clothing, skin color, etc. Volume 402 includes some "mug shot" photographs.
The minute books of the Board of Police Commissioners describe topics discussed at Board meetings, including commendations of particular patrolmen, a group of criminals that need to addressed, increasing YPD employee wages, expansions, etc. Also included are copies of Resolutions adopted by the Board.
Biographical/Historical Note
The Yonkers police force was formed in response to the influx of "transients" flooding the streets after the American Civil War. Newspapers described the existing town constables as "ineffective" and at a special town meeting a resolution was passed to hire fourteen Metropolitan officers from New York City to serve the community. These NYC police officers started in Yonkers on August 10, 1866, forming a substation of the New York 32nd Precinct.
By April 10, 1871, John T. Hoffman, the governor of New York signed an act that formed Yonkers' own local police force which consisted of one captain, two sergeants, two roundsmen, 18 patrolmen, 1 hostler and one doorman. The Captain of Police position was given to John Mangin who served as a sergeant in the original New York City Policemen stationed in Yonkers. The annual salary for a patrolman in Yonkers in 1871 was $750. Any man who was interested in becoming a Yonkers Policeman had to go through an interview with the Board of Commissioners and pass a medical examination by a police surgeon. No written examination was required. The appointment was for life, contingent on good behavior.
During the 1870's, the Yonkers Police Department had two sub-stations. The first sub-station was located in Kingsbridge, south of Yonkers. And the second location was in Bronxville. Patrolling of the town was carried out by foot patrol, mounted patrol and horse and wagon patrol. The mounted patrols were primarily used in the remote areas of Yonkers. Every policeman had two shifts; his first tour duty and his reserve duty. At the completion of his first shift, a policeman is required to remain at the station for an additional 8 hours. Beds were provided at the headquarters for sleeping. This requirement was to ensure that there was a sufficient amount of personnel should an emergency occur.
Access Restrictions
This collection is stored OFFSITE. Researchers wishing to view these materials must submit a request at least five (5) days in advance of the date of their library visit.
Open to qualified researchers.
Photocopying undertaken by staff only. Limited to ten exposures of stable, unbound material per day. (Researchers may not accrue unused copy amounts from previous days.) Researchers on site may print out unlimited copies from microfilm reader-printer machines at per-exposure rates. See guidelines in Reading Room for details.
Blotters (bookkeeping records); Criminals.; Police -- New York (State) -- Yonkers.; Westchester County (N.Y.)
- Series I: Yonkers Police Blotters, 1867 - 1907
  Location Note
  This collection is stored OFFSITE. Researchers wishing to view these materials must submit a request at least five (5) days in advance of the date of their library visit.
  - Blotter 1867-1868, November 1867 - 23 March 1868 (Offsite-volume 1)
  - Blotter 1868, 23 March 1868 - 28 August 1868 (Offsite-volume 2)
  - Blotter 1870-1871, 21 January 1870 - 28 May 1871 (Offsite-volume 3)
  - Blotter 1871, 15 March 1871 - 29 May 1871 (Offsite-volume 4)
  - Blotter 1872, 12 August 1872 (Offsite-volume 5)
  - Blotter 1872, 18 June 1872 (Offsite-volume 6)
  - Blotter 1873, 3 October 1873 - 31 October 1873 (Offsite-volume 7)
  - Blotter 1873, 7 December 1873 (Offsite-volume 8)
  - Blotter 1874, 10 January 1874 - 22 February 1874 (Offsite-volume 9)
  - Blotter 1874, 27 March 1874 - 27 April 1874 (Offsite-volume 10)
  - Blotter 1874, 12 May 1874 - 16 June 1874 (Offsite-volume 11)
  - Blotter 1874, 16 June 1874 - 24 July 1874 (Offsite-volume 12)
  - Blotter 1874, 24 July 1874 - 30 August 1874 (Offsite-volume 13)
  - Blotter 1874, 30 August 1874 - 6 October 1874 (Offsite-volume 14)
  - Blotter 1874, 12 November 1874 - 17 December 1874 (Offsite-volume 15)
  - Blotter 1875, 23 January 1875 - 1 March 1875 (Offsite-volume 16)
  - Blotter 1875, 1 March 1874 - 6 April 1875 (Offsite-volume 17)
  - Blotter 1875, 6 April 1875 - 11 May 1875 (Offsite-volume 18)
  - Blotter 1875, 11 May 1875 - 14 June 1875 (Offsite-volume 19)
  - Blotter 1875, 15 June 1875 - 17 July 1875 (Offsite-volume 20)
  - Blotter 1875, 17 July 1875 - 21 August 1875 (Offsite-volume 21)
  - Blotter 1875, 21 August 1875 - 22 September 1875 (Offsite-volume 22)
  - Blotter 1875, 22 September 1875 (Offsite-volume 23)
  - Blotter 1875, 27 October 1875 - 2 December 1875 (Offsite-volume 24)
  - Blotter 1875-1876, 2 December 1875 - 8 January 1876 (Offsite-volume 25)
  - Blotter 1876, 8 January 1876 - 15 February 1876 (Offsite-volume 26)
  - Blotter 1876, 15 February 1876 - 25 March 1876 (Offsite-volume 27)
  - Blotter 1876, 25 March 1876 - 29 April 1876 (Offsite-volume 28)
  - Blotter 1876, 29 April 1876 - 3 June 1876 (Offsite-volume 29)
  - Blotter 1876, 3 June 1876 - 8 July 1876 (Offsite-volume 30)
  - Blotter 1876, 8 July 1876 - 11 August 1876 (Offsite-volume 31)
  - Blotter 1876, 11 August 1876 - 16 September 1876 (Offsite-volume 32)
  - Blotter 1876, 16 September 1876 - 22 October 1876 (Offsite-volume 33)
  - Blotter 1876, 26 November 1876 - 30 December 1876 (Offsite-volume 34)
  - Blotter 1876-1877, 30 December 1876 - 5 February 1877 (Offsite-volume 35)
  - Blotter 1877, 5 February 1877 - 13 March 1877 (Offsite-volume 36)
  - Blotter 1877, 13 March 1877 - 16 April 1877 (Offsite-volume 37)
  - Blotter 1877, 16 April 1877 - 20 May 1877 (Offsite-volume 38)
  - Blotter 1877, 28 June 1877 - 31 July 1877 (Offsite-volume 39)
  - Blotter 1877, 1 August 1877 - 3 September 1877 (Offsite-volume 40)
  - Blotter 1877, 3 September 1877 - 7 October 1877 (Offsite-volume 41)
  - Blotter 1877, 7 October 1877 - 10 November 1877 (Offsite-volume 42)
  - Blotter 1877, 10 November 1877 - 14 December 1877 (Offsite-volume 43)
  - Blotter 1877-1878, 14 December 1877 - 19 January 1878 (Offsite-volume 44)
  - Blotter 1878, 19 January 1878 - 24 February 1878 (Offsite-volume 45)
  - Blotter 1878, 24 February 1878 - 31 March 1878 (Offsite-volume 46)
  - Blotter 1878, 31 March 1878 - 4 May 1878 (Offsite-volume 47)
  - Blotter 1878, 4 May 1878-8 June 1878 (Offsite-volume 407)
  - Blotter 1878, 8 June 1878 - 12 July 1878 (Offsite-volume 48)
  - Blotter 1878, 12 July 1878 - 13 August 1878 (Offsite-volume 49)
  - Blotter 1878, 14 August 1878 - 18 September 1878 (Offsite-volume 50)
  - Blotter 1878, 18 September 1878 - 22 October 1878 (Offsite-volume 51)
  - Blotter 1878, 22 October 1878 - 25 November 1878 (Offsite-volume 52)
  - Blotter 1878, 25 November 1878 - 27 December 1878 (Offsite-volume 53)
  - Blotter 1878-1879, 28 December 1878 - 1 February 1879 (Offsite-volume 54)
  - Blotter 1879, 10 March 1879 - 13 April 1879 (Offsite-volume 55)
  - Blotter 1879, 13 April 1879 - 17 May 1879 (Offsite-volume 56)
  - Blotter 1879, 17 May 1879 - 19 June 1879 (Offsite-volume 57)
  - Blotter 1879, 19 June 1879 - 21 July 1879 (Offsite-volume 58)
  - Blotter 1879, 21 July 1879 - 24 August 1879 (Offsite-volume 59)
  - Blotter 1879, 26 September 1879 - 30 October 1879 (Offsite-volume 60)
  - Blotter 1879, 30 October 1879 - 3 December 1879 (Offsite-volume 61)
  - Blotter 1879-1880, 3 December 1879 - 5 January 1880 (Offsite-volume 62)
  - Blotter 1880, 6 January 1880 - 9 February 1880 (Offsite-volume 63)
  - Blotter 1880, 9 February 1880 - 15 March 1880 (Offsite-volume 64)
  - Blotter 1880, 15 March 1880 - 19 April 1880 (Offsite-volume 65)
  - Blotter 1880, 19 April 1880 - 25 May 1880 (Offsite-volume 66)
  - Blotter 1880, 25 May 1880 - 29 June 1880 (Offsite-volume 67)
  - Blotter 1880, 29 June 1880 - 2 August 1880 (Offsite-volume 68)
  - Blotter 1880, 2 August 1880 - 6 September 1880 (Offsite-volume 69)
  - Blotter 1880, 7 September 1880 - 12 October 1880 (Offsite-volume 70)
  - Blotter 1880, 12 October 1880 - 15 November 1880 (Offsite-volume 71)
  - Blotter 1880, 16 November 1880 - 17 December 1880 (Offsite-volume 72)
  - Blotter 1880-1881, 17 December 1880 - 30 January 1881 (Offsite-volume 73)
  - Blotter 1881, 20 January 1881 - 23 February 1881 (Offsite-volume 74)
  - Blotter 1881, 23 February 1881 - 29 March 1881 (Offsite-volume 75)
  - Blotter 1881, 31 March 1881 - 3 May 1881 (Offsite-volume 76)
  - Blotter 1881, 3 May 1881 - 7 June 1881 (Offsite-volume 77)
  - Blotter 1881, 7 June 1881 - 12 July 1881 (Offsite-volume 78)
  - Blotter 1881, 12 July 1881 - 14 August 1881 (Offsite-volume 79)
  - Blotter 1881, 15 August 1881 - 20 September 1881 (Offsite-volume 80)
  - Blotter 1881, 20 September 1881 - 26 October 1881 (Offsite-volume 81)
  - Blotter 1881, 26 October 1881 - 30 November 1881 (Offsite-volume 82)
  - Blotter 1881-1882, 30 November 1881 - 6 January 1882 (Offsite-volume 83)
  - Blotter 1882, 6 January 1882 - 12 February 1882 (Offsite-volume 84)
  - Blotter 1882, 12 February 1882 - 21 March 1882 (Offsite-volume 85)
  - Blotter 1882, 22 March 1882 - 28 April 1882 (Offsite-volume 86)
  - Blotter 1882, 28 April 1882 - 4 June 1882 (Offsite-volume 87)
  - Blotter 1882, 5 June 1882 - 10 July 1882 (Offsite-volume 88)
  - Blotter 1882, 11 July 1882 - 17 August 1882 (Offsite-volume 89)
  - Blotter 1882, 17 August 1882 - 22 September 1882 (Offsite-volume 90)
  - Blotter 1882, 23 September 1882 - 28 October 1882 (Offsite-volume 91)
  - Blotter 1882, 28 October 1882 - 4 December 1882 (Offsite-volume 92)
  - Blotter 1882-1883, 4 December 1882 - 8 January 1883 (Offsite-volume 93)
  - Blotter 1883, 8 January 1883 - 12 February 1883 (Offsite-volume 94)
  - Blotter 1883, 12 February 1883 - 20 March 1883 (Offsite-volume 95)
  - Blotter 1883, 20 March 1883 - 25 April 1883 (Offsite-volume 96)
  - Blotter 1883, 25 April 1883 - 30 May 1883 (Offsite-volume 97)
  - Blotter 1883, 4 July 1883 - 8 August 1883 (Offsite-volume 98)
  - Blotter 1883, 9 August 1883 - 13 September 1883 (Offsite-volume 99)
  - Blotter 1883-1884, 27 November 1883 - 1 January 1884 (Offsite-volume 100)
  - Blotter 1883, 30 May 1883 - 4 July 1883 (Offsite-volume 101)
  - Blotter 1883, 13 September 1883 - 20 October 1883 (Offsite-volume 102)
  - Blotter 1883, 20 October 1883 - 26 November 1883 (Offsite-volume 103)
  - Blotter 1884, 1 January 1884 - 7 February 1884 (Offsite-volume 104)
  - Blotter 1884, 7 February 1884 - 14 March 1884 (Offsite-volume 105)
  - Blotter 1884, 14 March 1884 - 19 April 1884 (Offsite-volume 106)
  - Blotter 1884, 19 April 1884 - 24 May 1884 (Offsite-volume 107)
  - Blotter 1884, 24 May 1884 - 30 June 1884 (Offsite-volume 108)
  - Blotter 1884, 30 June 1884 - 6 August 1884 (Offsite-volume 109)
  - Blotter 1884, 6 August 1884 - 11 September 1884 (Offsite-volume 110)
  - Blotter 1884, 11 September 1884 - 17 October 1884 (Offsite-volume 111)
  - Blotter 1884-1885, 26 December 1884 - 3 January 1885 (Offsite-volume 112)
  - Blotter 1885, 30 January 1885 - 2 March 1885 (Offsite-volume 113)
  - Blotter 1885, 2 April 1885 - 3 May 1885 (Offsite-volume 114)
  - Blotter 1885, 3 May 1885 - 30 May 1885 (Offsite-volume 115)
  - Blotter 1885, 31 May 1885 - 29 June 1885 (Offsite-volume 116)
  - Blotter 1885, 30 July 1885 - 29 August 1885 (Offsite-volume 117)
  - Blotter 1885, 29 August 1885 - 1 October 1885 (Offsite-volume 118)
  - Blotter 1885, 1 October 1885 - 1 November 1885 (Offsite-volume 119)
  - Blotter 1885, 1 November 1885 - 3 December 1885 (Offsite-volume 120)
  - Blotter 1885-1886, 3 December 1885 - 4 January 1886 (Offsite-volume 121)
  - Blotter 1886, 28 January 1886 - 20 February 1886 (Offsite-volume 122)
  - Blotter 1886, 20 February 1886 - 13 March 1886 (Offsite-volume 123)
  - Blotter 1886, 14 March 1886 - 4 April 1886 (Offsite-volume 124)
  - Blotter 1886, 4 April 1886 - 26 April 1886 (Offsite-volume 125)
  - Blotter 1886, 26 April 1886 - 18 May 1886 (Offsite-volume 126)
  - Blotter 1886, 18 May 1886 - 9 June 1886 (Offsite-volume 127)
  - Blotter 1886, 9 June 1886 - 1 July 1886 (Offsite-volume 128)
  - Blotter 1886, 1 July 1886 - 25 July 1886 (Offsite-volume 129)
  - Blotter 1886, 25 July 1886 - 18 August 1886 (Offsite-volume 130)
  - Blotter 1886, 18 August 1886 - 25 September 1886 (Offsite-volume 131)
  - Blotter 1886, 25 September 1886 - 1 November 1886 (Offsite-volume 132)
  - Blotter 1886, 1 November 1886 - 6 December 1886 (Offsite-volume 148)
  - Blotter 1886-1887, 6 December 1886 - 11 January 1887 (Offsite-volume 133)
  - Blotter 1887, 11 January 1887 - 20 February 1887 (Offsite-volume 134)
  - Blotter 1887, 20 February 1887 - 2 April 1887 (Offsite-volume 135)
  - Blotter 1887, 2 April 1887 - 10 May 1887 (Offsite-volume 136)
  - Blotter 1887, 10 May 1887 - 17 June 1887 (Offsite-volume 137)
  - Blotter 1887, 17 June 1887 - 28 July 1887 (Offsite-volume 138)
  - Blotter 1887, 29 July 1887 - 4 September 1887 (Offsite-volume 139)
  - Blotter 1887, 5 September 1887 - 10 October 1887 (Offsite-volume 140)
  - Blotter 1887, 10 October 1887 - 15 November 1887 (Offsite-volume 141)
  - Blotter 1887, 15 November 1887 - 19 December 1887 (Offsite-volume 142)
  - Blotter 1887-1888, 20 December 1887 - 24 January 1888 (Offsite-volume 143)
  - Blotter 1888, 24 January 1888 - 2 March 1888 (Offsite-volume 144)
  - Blotter 1888, 2 March 1888 - 7 April 1888 (Offsite-volume 145)
  - Blotter 1888, 7 April 1888 - 13 May 1888 (Offsite-volume 146)
  - Blotter 1888, 13 May 1888 - 18 June 1888 (Offsite-volume 147)
  - Blotter 1888, 18 June 1888 - 26 July 1888 (Offsite-volume 149)
  - Blotter 1888, 26 July 1888 - 31 August 1888 (Offsite-volume 150)
  - Blotter 1888, 31 August 1888 - 5 October 1888 (Offsite-volume 151)
  - Blotter 1888, 9 November 1888 - 14 December 1888 (Offsite-volume 152)
  - Blotter 1888-1889, 14 December 1888 - 13 January 1889 (Offsite-volume 153)
  - Blotter 1889, 13 January 1889 - 19 February 1889 (Offsite-volume 154)
  - Blotter 1889, 19 February 1889 - 25 March 1889 (Offsite-volume 155)
  - Blotter 1889, 25 March 1889 - 26 April 1889 (Offsite-volume 156)
  - Blotter 1889, 26 April 1889 - 28 May 1889 (Offsite-volume 157)
  - Blotter 1889, 28 May 1889 - 29 June 1889 (Offsite-volume 158)
  - Blotter 1889, 30 June 1889 - 1 August 1889 (Offsite-volume 159)
  - Blotter 1889, 2 August 1889 - 3 September 1889 (Offsite-volume 160)
  - Blotter 1889, 3 September 1889 - 5 October 1889 (Offsite-volume 161)
  - Blotter 1889, 5 October 1889 - 7 November 1889 (Offsite-volume 162)
  - Blotter 1889, 7 November 1889 - 12 December 1889 (Offsite-volume 163)
  - Blotter 1889-1890, 12 December 1889 - 17 January 1890 (Offsite-volume 164)
  - Blotter 1890, 17 January 1890 - 20 February 1890 (Offsite-volume 165)
  - Blotter 1890, 20 February 1890 - 25 March 1890 (Offsite-volume 166)
  - Blotter 1890, 25 March 1890 - 27 April 1890 (Offsite-volume 167)
  - Blotter 1890, 27 April 1890 - 30 May 1890 (Offsite-volume 168)
  - Blotter 1890, 30 May 1890 - 6 July 1890 (Offsite-volume 169)
  - Blotter 1890, 6 July 1890 - 26 July 1890 (Offsite-volume 170)
  - Blotter 1890, 26 July 1890 - 29 August 1890 (Offsite-volume 171)
  - Blotter 1890, 29 August 1890 - 30 September 1890 (Offsite-volume 172)
  - Blotter 1890, 30 September 1890 - 1 November 1890 (Offsite-volume 173)
  - Blotter 1890, 1 November 1890 - 6 December 1890 (Offsite-volume 174)
  - Blotter 1890-1891, 6 December 1890 - 10 January 1891 (Offsite-volume 175)
  - Blotter 1891, 10 January 1891 - 14 February 1891 (Offsite-volume 176)
  - Blotter 1891, 14 February 1891 - 21 March 1891 (Offsite-volume 177)
  - Blotter 1891, 21 March 1891 - 24 April 1891 (Offsite-volume 178)
  - Blotter 1891, 24 April 1891 - 28 May 1891 (Offsite-volume 179)
  - Blotter 1891, 29 May 1891 - 1 July 1891 (Offsite-volume 180)
  - Blotter 1891, 1 July 1891 - 4 August 1891 (Offsite-volume 181)
  - Blotter 1891, 4 August 1891 - 6 September 1891 (Offsite-volume 182)
  - Blotter 1891, 6 September 1891 - 10 October 1891 (Offsite-volume 183)
  - Blotter 1891, 10 October 1891 - 12 November 1891 (Offsite-volume 184)
  - Blotter 1891, 12 November 1891 - 18 December 1891 (Offsite-volume 185)
  - Blotter 1891-1892, 18 December 1891 - 22 January 1892 (Offsite-volume 186)
  - Blotter 1892, 22 January 1892 - 25 February 1892 (Offsite-volume 187)
  - Blotter 1892, 25 February 1892 - 22 March 1892 (Offsite-volume 188)
  - Blotter 1892, 30 March 1892 - 3 May 1892 (Offsite-volume 189)
  - Blotter 1892, 3 May 1892 - 9 June 1892 (Offsite-volume 190)
  - Blotter 1892, 9 June 1892 - 25 August 1892 (Offsite-volume 191)
  - Blotter 1892, 26 August 1892 - 1 October 1892 (Offsite-volume 192)
  - Blotter 1892, 1 October 1892 - 7 November 1892 (Offsite-volume 193)
  - Blotter 1892, 7 November 1892 - 13 December 1892 (Offsite-volume 194)
  - Blotter 1892-1893, 13 December 1892 - 8 January 1893 (Offsite-volume 195)
  - Blotter 1893, 8 January 1893 - 4 February 1893 (Offsite-volume 196)
  - Blotter 1893, 4 February 1893 - 4 March 1893 (Offsite-volume 197)
  - Blotter 1893, 4 March 1893 - 29 March 1893 (Offsite-volume 198)
  - Blotter 1893, 29 March 1893 - 22 April 1893 (Offsite-volume 199)
  - Blotter 1893, 22 April 1893 - 18 May 1893 (Offsite-volume 200)
  - Blotter 1893, 18 May 1893 - 12 June 1893 (Offsite-volume 201)
  - Blotter 1893, 12 June 1893 - 7 July 1893 (Offsite-volume 202)
  - Blotter 1893, 7 July 1893 - 1 August 1893 (Offsite-volume 203)
  - Blotter 1893, 1 August 1893 - 26 August 1893 (Offsite-volume 204)
  - Blotter 1893, 26 August 1893 - 21 September 1893 (Offsite-volume 205)
  - Blotter 1893, 21 September 1893 - 17 October 1893 (Offsite-volume 206)
  - Blotter 1893, 17 October 1893 - 12 November 1893 (Offsite-volume 207)
  - Blotter 1893, 12 November 1893 - 7 December 1893 (Offsite-volume 208)
  - Blotter 1893-1894, 7 December 1893 - 1 January 1894 (Offsite-volume 209)
  - Blotter 1894, 1 January 1894 - 26 January 1894 (Offsite-volume 210)
  - Blotter 1894, 26 January 1894 - 20 February 1894 (Offsite-volume 211)
  - Blotter 1894, 20 February 1894 - 17 March 1894 (Offsite-volume 212)
  - Blotter 1894, 17 March 1894 - 10 April 1894 (Offsite-volume 213)
  - Blotter 1894, 10 April 1894 - 3 May 1894 (Offsite-volume 214)
  - Blotter 1894, 12 May 1894 - 28 May 1894 (Offsite-volume 215)
  - Blotter 1894, 28 May 1894 - 19 June 1894 (Offsite-volume 216)
  - Blotter 1894, 19 June 1894 - 12 July 1894 (Offsite-volume 217)
  - Blotter 1894, 12 July 1894 - 5 August 1894 (Offsite-volume 218)
  - Blotter 1894, 5 August 1894 - 25 September 1894 (Offsite-volume 219)
  - Blotter 1894, 25 September 1894 - 21 October 1894 (Offsite-volume 220)
  - Blotter 1894, 21 October 1894 - 12 November 1894 (Offsite-volume 221)
  - Blotter 1894, 12 November 1894 - 8 December 1894 (Offsite-volume 222)
  - Blotter 1894-1895, 8 December 1894 - 1 January 1895 (Offsite-volume 223)
  - Blotter 1895, 1 January 1895 - 23 January 1895; yonkers (Offsite-volume 224)
  - Blotter 1895, 23 January 1895 - 14 February 1895 (Offsite-volume 225)
  - Blotter 1895, 14 February 1895 -7 March 1895 (Offsite-volume 226)
  - Blotter 1895, 7 March 1895 - 29 March 1895 (Offsite-volume 227)
  - Blotter 1895, 29 March 1895 - 19 April 1895 (Offsite-volume 228)
  - Blotter 1895, 19 April 1895 - 12 May 1895 (Offsite-volume 229)
  - Blotter 1895, 12 May 1895 - 12 June 1895 (Offsite-volume 230)
  - Blotter 1895, 12 June 1895 - 25 June 1895 (Offsite-volume 231)
  - Blotter 1895, 25 June 1895 - 16 July 1895 (Offsite-volume 232)
  - Blotter 1895, 16 July 1895 - 8 August 1895 (Offsite-volume 233)
  - Blotter 1895, 8 August 1895 - 21 August 1895 (Offsite-volume 234)
  - Blotter 1895, 21 August 1895 - 21 September 1895 (Offsite-volume 235)
  - Blotter 1895, 21 September 1895 - 14 October 1895 (Offsite-volume 236)
  - Blotter 1895, 14 October 1895 - 5 November 1895 (Offsite-volume 237)
  - Blotter 1895, 5 November 1895 - 27 November 1895 (Offsite-volume 238)
  - Blotter 1895, 27 November 1895 - 17 December 1895 (Offsite-volume 239)
  - Blotter 1895-1896, 17 December 1895 - 7 January 1896 (Offsite-volume 240)
  - Blotter 1896, 7 January 1896 - 29 January 1896 (Offsite-volume 241)
  - Blotter 1896, 29 January 1896 - 20 February 1896 (Offsite-volume 242)
  - Blotter 1896, 20 February 1896 - 13 March 1896 (Offsite-volume 243)
  - Blotter 1896, 13 March 1896 - 5 April 1896 (Offsite-volume 244)
  - Blotter 1896, 5 April 1896 - 26 April 1896 (Offsite-volume 245)
  - Blotter 1896, 26 April 1896 - 18 May 1896 (Offsite-volume 246)
  - Blotter 1896, 18 May 1896 - 9 June 1896 (Offsite-volume 247)
  - Blotter 1896, 9 June 1896 - 1 July 1896 (Offsite-volume 248)
  - Blotter 1896, 1 July 1896 - 23 July 1896 (Offsite-volume 249)
  - Blotter 1896, 23 July 1896 - 13 August 1896 (Offsite-volume 250)
  - Blotter 1896, 13 August 1896 - 5 September 1896 (Offsite-volume 251)
  - Blotter 1896, 5 September 1896 - 25 September 1896 (Offsite-volume 252)
  - Blotter 1896, 26 September 1896 - 16 October 1896 (Offsite-volume 253)
  - Blotter 1896, 16 October 1896 - 6 November 1896 (Offsite-volume 254)
  - Blotter 1896, 6 November 1896 - 27 November 1896 (Offsite-volume 255)
  - Blotter 1896, 28 November 1896 - 19 December 1896 (Offsite-volume 256)
  - Blotter 1896-1897, 19 December 1896 - 10 January 1897 (Offsite-volume 257)
  - Blotter 1897, 10 January 1897 - 31 January 1897 (Offsite-volume 258)
  - Blotter 1897, 31 January 1897 - 23 February 1897 (Offsite-volume 259)
  - Blotter 1897, 23 February 1897 - 16 March 1897 (Offsite-volume 260)
  - Blotter 1897, 16 March 1897 - 7 April 1897 (Offsite-volume 261)
  - Blotter 1897, 7 April 1897 - 29 April 1897 (Offsite-volume 262)
  - Blotter 1897, 29 April 1897 - 20 May 1897 (Offsite-volume 263)
  - Blotter 1897, 20 May 1897 - 10 June 1897 (Offsite-volume 264)
  - Blotter 1897, 10 June 1897 - 21 July 1897 (Offsite-volume 265)
  - Blotter 1897, 21 July 1897 - 12 August 1897 (Offsite-volume 266)
  - Blotter 1897, 12 August 1897 - 2 September 1897 (Offsite-volume 267)
  - Blotter 1897, 2 September 1897 - 22 September 1897 (Offsite-volume 268)
  - Blotter 1897, 22 September 1897 - 13 October 1897 (Offsite-volume 269)